football-wallpapers.com 2009-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Football Wallpapers, Videos, Myspace Layouts

Football-Wallpapers.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Third Party Advertising  
We use Google AdSense ( ), ValueClick a.k.a. FastClick (

) and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Personal Information  
This Web site does allow user to enter their email address at their own will for comments on our site. We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. Football-Wallpapers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.football-wallpapers.com/contact-us/).

﻿

Football-Wallpapers.com News

All wallpapers containing FC Bayern München logo, The Premier League's clubs' logos and Premier League logo have been removed from the site. [Read more...](http://www.football-wallpapers.com/dmca-letter/)

Advertisement

Mobile Stuff

Are you looking for quality and exclusive downloadable mobile (cell) phone stuff for most mobile (cell) phone models? Then you should visit Football-Wallpapers.com [Mobile Stuff](http://footwalls.ringtone-logo-game.com/0-000/uk_en/home/index.html "Mobile Stuff") site where you can find the largest database of:  
**Music** : True Tones, Cover Tones, Polyphonic Ringtones, Monophonic Ringtones, Crazy Ringtones, Real Sounds, MP3  
**Pictures** : Colour Wallpapers, Screensavers, My Own Pic, Motorola Packs, Nokia Packs, Sony-Ericsson Packs, Custom Color Logos, Avatar Logos, Animated, Themes, Clipart  
**Java** : Java Games, Java Applications  
**Videos** : Animals, Babes, Car/Moto, Events/Parties, Fun, Love, Movies, Music, Sexy, Space/Scenery, Sports, Tekno Dance, Toons
